{
    "subject": "resource/List_of_Super_Dave_Osborne_Show_episodes",
    "predicate": "property/shortsummary",
    "object": "Glen Campbell sings \"On a Good Night\". Super and Donald give a tour of the new Super Dave Senior Citizen's Theatre, which has features specifically built for senior citizens and their needs. The movie playing is Super's \"Garbane\" fuel demonstration. Super find out the building was renovated, and he wonders what the building used to be. Donald tells him it used to be a Senior Citizen's parking lot.\n\nThe Super One gets hurt: \"Of course\u2026\" Gladys, a senior lady, still thinks it's a parking lot, and drives through the screen flattening him.\n\nThe Last Word: He pleads with everyone for help. \n\nArrival Vehicle:  The Super dave black motorbike and sidecar.\n\nMike Walden's Outfit: Pale Peach jacket, red tie, white hanky and shirt, white pants and shoes.",
    "human_readable": "The short summary of List of Super Dave Osborne Show episodes is: Glen Campbell sings 'On a Good Night'. Super and Donald give a tour of the new Super Dave Senior Citizen's Theatre, which has features specifically built for senior citizens and their needs. The movie playing is Super's 'Garbane' fuel demonstration. Super finds out the building was renovated, and he wonders what the building used to be. Donald tells him it used to be a Senior Citizen's parking lot.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.7908682823181152,
            "question": "What is the name of the theatre Super and Donald tour?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7831907272338867,
            "question": "What demonstration does Super give at the theatre?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7813490629196167,
            "question": "What kind of features does the Senior Citizen's Theatre have?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.741969108581543,
            "question": "What was the building that houses the Senior Citizen's Theatre before it became a theatre?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7187362313270569,
            "question": "Who tells Super what the building used to be?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7145177721977234,
            "question": "What song does Glen Campbell sing on the show?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6871002912521362,
            "question": "What is the name of Super's film demonstration?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5633641481399536,
            "question": "What movie is playing at the theatre?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3872833847999573,
            "question": "Does Super seem surprised about the building's history?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.34273654222488403,
            "question": "What type of show is this episode?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The short summary of List of Super Dave Osborne Show episodes is: Glen Campbell sings 'On a Good Night'. Super and Donald give a tour of the new Super Dave Senior Citizen's Theatre, which has features specifically built for senior citizens and their needs. The movie playing is Super's 'Garbane' fuel demonstration. Super finds out the building was renovated, and he wonders what the building used to be. Donald tells him it used to be a Senior Citizen's parking lot.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2568_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does Super seem surprised about the building's history?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2568_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What movie is playing at the theatre?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2568_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Super's film demonstration?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2568_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2568_112.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2568_134.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2568_138.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2568_142.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2568_169.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2568_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2568_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2568_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2568_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2568_81.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\nThe provided summary does not mention any information about List of Super Dave Osborne Show episodes.  It describes scenes from a specific episode or collection of episodes, but doesn't offer an overall summary of the entire show's list of episodes."
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the context information provided, I will evaluate whether the statement about the summary of List of Super Dave Osborne Show episodes is correct.\n\nQuery: The short summary of List of Super Dave Osborne Show episodes is: Glen Campbell sings 'On a Good Night'. Super and Donald give a tour of the new Super Dave Senior Citizen's Theatre, which has features specifically built for senior citizens and their needs. The movie playing is Super's 'Garbane' fuel demonstration. Super finds out the building was renovated, and he wonders what the building used to be. Donald tells him it used to be a Senior Citizen's parking lot.\n\nResponse: \n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "It contradicts the information provided later about Super Dave's museum of modern art, which implies a different location for the Senior Citizen's Theatre.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}